export const page10ex3 = [
  [
    {
      question: 'A. you / eat /junk food, Juan?',
      answer: 'Do you eat junk food, Juan?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B. No / I',
      answer: 'No, I don\'t',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A. you / do / a lot of sport, Kika?',
      answer: 'Do you do a lot of sport, Kika?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: Yes / I',
      answer: 'Yes, I do',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: the students in your class / live / near you?',
      answer: 'Do the students in your class live near you?',
    },
    {
      question: 'No / they',
      answer: 'No, they don\'t',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: you and Clara / like / Italian food?',
      answer: 'Do you and Clara like Italian food?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: Yes / we',
      answer: 'Yes, we do',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: you / listen / Radio 5, Daniel?',
      answer: 'Do you listen to Radio 5, Daniel?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: Yes / I',
      answer: 'Yes, I do',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: Ursula and Hans / study / English with you?',
      answer: 'Do Ursula and Hans study English with you?',
    },
    {
      question: 'No / they',
      answer: 'No, they don\'t',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: I / have / classes on Saturday?',
      answer: 'Do I have classes on Saturday?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: No / you',
      answer: 'No, you don\'t',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: you and your family / eat / together?',
      answer: 'Do you and your family eat together?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: Yes / we',
      answer: 'Yes, we do',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: Ali and Marco / play / tennis?',
      answer: 'Do Ali and Marco play tennis?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: Yes / they',
      answer: 'Yes, they do',
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'A: you and Ana / drink / coffee?',
      answer: 'Do you and Ana drink coffee?',
    },
    {
      question: 'B: No / we',
      answer: 'No, we don\'t',
    },
  ],
];
